# Mantey Caleb Edem Komla

P.O BOX, ML 598 Mallam – Accra Gender - Male +233 57 887 6149 - Email: manteycaleb@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

Selfless and a hardworking team player with skillset ranging from game development to web development. A dedicated and efficiently self-taught full stack web developer with 3+ years' experience in various full stack web technologies and also 3 years of unity3d games development and creating 3d simulations as well as AR and VR experiences.

#### ACHIEVEMENTS

- GRAF Robotics Challenge Winners (September, 2012)
- GRAF Robotics Challenge First Runner Ups (September, 2013)
- University of Mines and Technology NUGS Award Best Student in IT (March, 2018)
- University of Mines and Technology Innovation and Career Fair First Runner Ups (April, 2018)
- HackLabGH Hackathon First Runner Ups (April, 2018)
- University of Mines and Technology Excellence Awards 2018 (UMEX 2018) Most Innovative Students (April, 2018)
- HackLabGH Hackathon Best Solution Education Category Award (April, 2019)

#### LEADERSHIP ROLES

Bishop Herman College Robotics Club – Vice President Geomatic Engineering Students Association – Vice President 2013 - 2014

2017 - 2018

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Ghana Armed Forces

September, 2019 – to date

**Task:** Creating military experiences for training new recruits and enhancing military tech through AR and VR

- Unity3d Developer
- 3d Modeler/Animator
- Virtual and Augmented Reality Developer

Stanbic Bank

May, 2019 – August, 2019

**Task:** Developing banking web apps and integrating with 3<sup>rd</sup> party systems

• Web Developer (Junior Full Stack)

Ghatty Foods, Mallam/Accra

*May*, 2017 – July, 2017

**Task:** Building professional websites and apps for providing useful information on products of the company.

- Full Stack Web Developer
- Mobile and Desktop App Developer

### **EDUCATION**

BSC Geomatic Engineering, University of Mines and Technology WASSCE, Bishop Herman College

2015 – 2019

2011 - 2014

## **SKILLS**

Web Development Game Development with Unity3d Rest Api's

## PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Html5, css3, JavaScript, php, java, c#, vb, c++, node

Augmented and Virtual Reality

# FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

ionic, electron, angular, react/react native, Vue, express, spring boot framework, mongo dB

## **HOBBIES & INTERESTS**

Love creating and playing computer games. Love exercising and doing lots of sports.